japaneseslurp.com 2017-09-03

# JapaneseSlurp.com - Privacy Statement

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on JapaneseSlurp.com and all websites in the network.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you sign up our sites, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When signing up on our sites, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your - name, e-mail address, mailing address and billing information (as a credit card number). You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our websites (we continually strive to improve our websites offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to yur computer`s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Cookies are used for a variety of purposes. For instance, when you return to the Site after logging in, cookies provide information to the Site so that the Site will remember you. We may also use temporary or "session" cookies to help you watch videos. These cookies will expire when you place an order. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Google Chrome or Safari) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your experience on the Site smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services will not function properly. Some of our business partners may also use cookies on the Site; however, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies and do not accept any responsibility for such use.

The Site use a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in code on the pages of web sites. We may use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on the Site, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the Site. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf.

The Site includes third party advertising and links to other web sites. These companies are called "network advertisers". We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these network advertisers. Network advertisers who place advertisements on the Site, or third parties with whom we have a relationship, may also use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information. You may not realize this information is being collected. In some cases, we may have access to information from web beacons and cookies used by network advertisers on the Site and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated with the network advertiser. Once you have clicked on an advertisement and have left the Site, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our websites at <http://japaneseslurp.com/terms>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our on-line privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Questions and Contact Information**

All questions to  regarding these terms and conditions must be directed to: 

registered address at 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](https://www.supportidols.com/).
